fansconnectonline.com 2011-05-17

# MTN FansConnectOnline Nigeria :: How to play

This Privacy Policy is effective as of December 20, 2009 ("Effective Date").   
Please read all of this Privacy Policy as very carefully prior to commencing use of this web site and on each and every occasion that you use this web site in the future to check for updates.   
The Privacy Policy applies to personal information that may be collected when you interact with Fans Connect Online or any of its subsidiaries ("www.fansconnectonline.com"). Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is our priority, and we believe that a single, comprehensive privacy policy that is straightforward and clear is in the best interests of our customers and our businesses. Any personal information provided or gathered via this web site is controlled primarily by Fans Connect Online.

By interacting with Fans Connect Online in the manner described in this Privacy Policy at any time on or after the Effective Date, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the application of this Privacy Policy to the collection, storage, use and disclosure of all your personal information as described.   
Fans Connect Online reserves the right to modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time, but you can be assured that, should it be necessary to do so, we will inform you and will always do so in accordance with the Fans Connect Online Principles of Clarity, Security and Integrity.

This Privacy Policy addresses the following questions:   
1\. What is the personal information that we collect?  
2\. Why do we collect personal information?  
3\. How do we collect your personal information?  
4\. How do we use personal information?  
5\. With whom do we share personal information?  
6\. How do we secure personal information?  
7\. How do we respect your choices about your personal information?  
8\. Whom do I contact if I have questions or concerns?

**1\. WHAT IS THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT?**  
Your personal information is not collected from you automatically, simply as a result of your accessing this web site. It is only collected on a voluntary basis, resulting from your own input of this information. The only information that is collected automatically when you access this web site is the IP address of the computer that you are using. For more information on IP addresses, please see below. 

If you register your personal details with this web site, it is only known to Fans Connect Online and trusted third party suppliers of related services. If you choose to register, Fans Connect Online will request information such as your name, email address, address, telephone number(s) or other contact details as required. Address (Home or Office) is needed to in order to deliver your gifts to you. This is applicable to our Nigerian resident members only. This information will then be held by Fans Connect Online to carry out the services for which you registered. Fans Connect Online will also use this information to improve the function of the web site and to prevent any abuse to the web site.   
Fans Connect Online will also keep any correspondence you send whether by email or standard mail. This correspondence will not be kept indefinitely, only for the statutory period. 

**2\. WHY DO WE COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
We collect your personal information in an effort to provide you with a superior member experience and, as necessary, to administer our business. It allows us to provide you with easy access to our network, with a particular focus on the items and programs that may be of most interest to you.   
As a general principle, your personal data will NOT be passed or sold to any third party except for as set out in this Privacy Policy or with your express permission. For more information as to why we collect personal information, please see the section below entitled: "How do we use your personal information?"

**3\. HOW DO WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
(a) Information that you provide to us.

As a general matter, you can browse in our website without submitting your personal information to us. However, there are a number of circumstances in which you may need to provide us with your personal information. The most common of these circumstances include:   
• Enrolling as a Member or joining a Fans Connect Online interactive fans community  
• Submitting a comment, a list, or other user-created content   
• Signing up for Newsletters and Alerts   
• Creating a "Fans" Profile   
• Contacting customer service  
For your convenience, we have provided a summary description of some of these circumstances below.  

Enrolling in our Member or joining a Hardcover Limited online interactive community  
When you enroll as a Member, we will ask you to submit personal information as part of your Member profile. The personal information you submit is held in a Member database.  
Submitting a comment, a list, or other user-created content  
You may choose to submit a member’s comment online on a match or to participate in Fans Connect Online live commentary. Because any information you post such as comments or live commentary will be available on the Internet, we can make no assurances that others will not use, or misuse, that information.

Signing up for Newsletters and Alerts  
You may choose to sign up for Newsletters and Alerts filled with tips, events and information on fan groups. You can choose to subscribe or unsubscribe later in your member profile.  
Creating a “Fans” Profile  
When you create your fans profile, we will ask you to submit personal information that would be displayed on your profile with your permission.  
Contacting Customer Service  
When you contact customer service, we may ask you to provide, or confirm, personal information so that we can better serve you.

(b) Information automatically collected

There are circumstances in which we automatically receive and collect personal information from you. The most common of these circumstances include:  
• Cookies   
• Occasionally from members, business partners, investors, shared databases, and other third parties  
For your convenience, we have provided a summary description of some of these circumstances below. 

Information automatically collected when you visit our websites

When you visit our websites, we automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. For example, we may receive and collect: the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet Protocol (IP) address of the computer you are using; the date and time you access our websites; and the Internet address of the website from which you linked directly to our sites. We use this information to monitor the usage of our websites and as necessary for our business. This information does not include personal information.

Information collected using cookies

We use cookies to personalize and enhance your browsing and shopping experience. Cookies are small files that we place on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our websites. Cookies help us to: (1) speed navigation, keep track of items you order to read, and provide you with content that is tailored to you; (2) remember information you gave us so that you don't have to re-enter it; (3) determine the effectiveness of some of our marketing efforts and communications; and (4) monitor the total number of visitors, pages viewed, and the total number of banners displayed.

Information collected from outside sources

We may periodically collect personal information and other information about you from business partners, investors and other third parties.

Information collected from visitors from outside Nigeria

It should be stated clearly that; Hardcover Limited is here to serve customers only in Nigeria and would by no means collect information from anyone who requires our services beyond Nigeria.

**4\. HOW DO WE USE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
Fans Connect Online uses your personal information to provide you with a superior customer experience at our libraries and on our website and, as necessary, to administer our business. For example, we use your personal information to:  
• Provide you tips, quiz, services and information, including the Fans Connect Online website and online interactive communities;  
• Administer contests, promotions or surveys;  
• Provide superior customer service;  
• Conduct research and perform analysis in order to measure, maintain, protect, develop and improve our services;  
• Communicate with you about events, or updates that may be of interest to you;  
• Customize and enhance our website and advertising;  
• Make communications necessary to notify you regarding security, privacy, and administrative issues;  
• Manage the fans community

**5\. WITH WHOM DO WE SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
Protecting the privacy and security of your personal information is a priority at Fans Connect Online. FANSCONNECTONLINE DOES NOT SELL OR RENT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES.

Fans Connect Online shares your personal information with:  
• Service providers, Delivery agencies and agents who perform services on our behalf. These third parties do not have the right to use personal information we provide to them in any way that is not authorized by Fans Connect Online. They are contractually obligated to use such information only as necessary to assist us and to maintain the confidentiality and security of such information.   
• Debit Card Companies. Debit card transactions are handled by third party financial institutions and their vendors and contractors who receive Debit card numbers and other personal information directly to verify the Debit card numbers and process transactions.  
• Law enforcement officials and as required by law. Fans Connect Online may release personal information to third parties when we determine, in our judgment, that it is necessary to (a) comply with the law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request; (b) enforce or apply the terms of any of our policies or user agreements; or (c) protect the rights, property or safety of Fans Connect Online, our employees, users, or others.

**6\. HOW DO WE SECURE PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
We take significant and appropriate security measures, including physical, technological and procedural measures, to help to safeguard your personal information and to prevent unauthorized access and disclosure. We use industry-standard technology, such as firewalls and encryption in the transmission of certain sensitive personal information, designed to prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your personal information.

We want you to feel confident whenever you visit us in our website. While we are focused on the security of your personal information and follow strict standards, processes and procedures that are designed to protect your personal information, we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information will remain secure in all circumstances.

**7\. HOW DO WE RESPECT YOUR CHOICE ABOUT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
When you are a fan on the Fans Connect Online community in certain ways, you may be eligible to receive certain marketing-related and promotional communications as well as special offers that may include advertisements from third parties. The most common of these circumstances include:  
• Quiz or tips  
• Creating a fans profile or join the Fans Connect Online community   
• Signing up for Newsletters and Alerts  
If, at any time, you wish to no longer receive Promotional Communications from Fans Connect Online please follow the instructions below.  
• For Hardcover Limited Member program: Any Member can opt-out of the receipt of any Member program promotional communications by logging on to their fansconnectonline.com Account and following the instructions under "Edit Account." If you do not have a fansconnectonline.com account, you may opt-out of the receipt of such communications by selecting the link at the bottom of any promotional e-mail communication and following the instructions.  
Even if you opt out of receiving Promotional Communications and newsletters you may continue to receive e-mails relating to game eligibility, fans position, and/or other business-related communications.

Note for Community Users

Fans Connect Online provides you with the ability to access; correct or change the personal information in your community profile(s) at any time. However, you cannot currently change your profile name although you may re-register and choose a new name. Please be advised that Hardcover Limited may archive information it collects on its community and visitors. 

**8\. WHOM DO I CONTACT IF I HAVE QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS?**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at privacy@fansconnectonline.com
